(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],[,,,,function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(11)},,,,,function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),r=n.n(a),s=n(3),o=n.n(s),c=(n(9),n(1));n(10);var i=function(e){return r.a.createElement("h3",null,"Question ",e.currentQuestion," of ",e.total)};var l=function(e){return r.a.createElement("h2",null,e.question)};var u=function(e){var t=["answer"];return e.selected&&t.push("selected"),r.a.createElement("button",{value:e.letter,className:t.join(" "),onClick:e.handleClick},r.a.createElement("span",{className:"letter"},e.letter),e.answer)};var d=function(e){return r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement(u,{letter:"a",answer:e.question.answer_a,handleClick:e.handleClick,selected:"a"===e.currentAnswer}),r.a.createElement(u,{letter:"b",answer:e.question.answer_b,handleClick:e.handleClick,selected:"b"===e.currentAnswer}),r.a.createElement(u,{letter:"c",answer:e.question.answer_c,handleClick:e.handleClick,selected:"c"===e.currentAnswer}),r.a.createElement(u,{letter:"d",answer:e.question.answer_d,handleClick:e.handleClick,selected:"d"===e.currentAnswer}))};var w=function(){var e=Object(a.useState)(0),t=Object(c.a)(e,2),n=t[0],s=t[1],o=Object(a.useState)(""),u=Object(c.a)(o,2),w=u[0],m=u[1],_=Object(a.useState)([]),h=Object(c.a)(_,2),b=h[0],f=h[1],p=Object(a.useState)(""),k=Object(c.a)(p,2),v=k[0],E=k[1],q=Object(a.useState)(!1),C=Object(c.a)(q,2),g=C[0],y=C[1],S=[{id:1,question:"What is ReactJS?",answer_a:"Server side framework",answer_b:"User-interface framework",answer_c:"Library for building interaction interfaces",answer_d:"Library for building responsive website",correct_answer:"b"},{id:2,question:"React is mainly used for building ___.",answer_a:"Database",answer_b:"User interface",answer_c:"Design Platform",answer_d:"Conectivity",correct_answer:"b"},{id:3,question:"Ref is used for referring an element or component returned by ___.",answer_a:"refer()",answer_b:"reduce()",answer_c:"render()",answer_d:"react()",correct_answer:"a"},{id:4,question:"Which statement about Hooks is not true?",answer_a:"Hooks are completely opt-in, ther`s no need to rewrite existing code",answer_b:"Hooks are still in beta and not available yet",answer_c:"Hooks are 100% backwards-compatibile and can be used side by side with classes",answer_d:"All of the above",correct_answer:"c"},{id:5,question:"Which one is not a Hook?",answer_a:"useState()",answer_b:"useConst()",answer_c:"useReducer()",answer_d:"All of the above",correct_answer:"b"},{id:6,question:"The arbitrary inputs of components are called ___.",answer_a:"Keys",answer_b:"Components",answer_c:"Ref",answer_d:"Href",correct_answer:"a"},{id:7,question:"What will happen if you call setState() inside render() method?",answer_a:"Repetitive output appears on the screen",answer_b:"Duplicate key error",answer_c:"Stack overflow error",answer_d:"Nothing happens",correct_answer:"c"},{id:8,question:"Which of the following is the correct syntax for a button click event handler foo?",answer_a:"<button onclick={this.foo()}>",answer_b:"<button onclick={this.foo}>",answer_c:"<button onClick={this.foo()}>",answer_d:"<button onClick={this.foo}>",correct_answer:"d"},{id:9,question:"Which of the following methods in a React Component is called after the component is rendered for the first time?",answer_a:"componentDidUpdate",answer_b:"componentDidMount",answer_c:"componentMounted",answer_d:"componentUpdated",correct_answer:"a"},{id:10,question:"What is used to pass data to a component from outside?",answer_a:"setStates",answer_b:"props",answer_c:"fetch",answer_d:"render with arguments",correct_answer:"d"}],j=S[n];return g?r.a.createElement("div",{className:"container results"},r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Result:"),r.a.createElement("ul",null,b.map((function(e){var t=S.find((function(t){return t.id===e.questionId}));return r.a.createElement("div",{key:t.id},t.question," - ",function(e,t){return e.correct_answer===t.answer?r.a.createElement("span",{className:"correct"},"Correct"):r.a.createElement("span",{className:"failed"},"Failed")}(t,e))}))),r.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary",onClick:function(){f([]),m(""),s(0),y(!1)}},"Restart")):r.a.createElement("div",{className:"main-container"},r.a.createElement("h1",null,"React quiz"),r.a.createElement(i,{total:S.length,currentQuestion:n+1}),r.a.createElement(l,{question:j.question}),function(){if(v)return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"error"},v)}(),r.a.createElement(d,{question:j,currentAnswer:w,handleClick:function(e){m(e.target.value),E("")}}),r.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary",onClick:function(){var e={questionId:j.id,answer:w};w?(b.push(e),f(b),m(""),n+1<S.length?s(n+1):y(!0)):E("Please select one option")}},"Confirm and continue"))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));o.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(w,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}],[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.eee4fd41.chunk.js.map